It's under my feet, it's under my feet.
The petitions can't get verified.
As much as he likes to play with the Republicans,
he still has a job in a doing particular black women in Georgia.
But he drops the appeal.
He can drop the appeal right now, but he refuses.
He refuses the way we see in refusing to call for a ceasefire and pour money.
Mayor Dickens, I want you to pay attention right now
because you in the South, welcome to Atlanta, the South.
The South got something to say, and it means something significant
when a group of black women and femmes come together dressed down and all white
with this rain pouring down on us.
I hope you got your people looking out for you, Mayor Dickens,
because our people are looking out for us for sure,
and they're not going to let you continue on like this.
From Atlanta to Palestine, our freedom is guaranteed.
Say, bust down that wall!
Bust down that wall!
Take back our freedom!